Inventory of the George Haven Putnam papers, circa 1800-1931
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- CORRESPONDENCE:
  - Putnam to Lord Loch., 7-1-1927 (Box 8)
  - H. R. Amory to Major Putnam., 7-1-1927 (Box 8)
  - Fosdick to Mr. Putnam., 7-8-1927 (Box 8)
  - Gregory Foster to Major Putnam., 7-9-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Raymond Blaine Fosdick., 7-11-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Harry Emerson Fosdick., 7-11-1927 (Box 8)
  - Harry Emerson Fosdick to Mr. Putnam., 7-18-1927 (Box 8)
  - Lord Loch to Major Putnam., 7-21-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Sir Gragory Foster., 7-21-1927 (Box 8)
  - Parmely W. Herrick to Putnam., 7-23-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Lord Loch., 8-3-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Sir Gregory Foster., 8-3-1927 (Box 8)
  - E. Marion Bryce to Dr. Putnam., 8-12-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Lord Loch., 8-15-1927 (Box 8)
  - William Howard Taft to Mr. Putnam., 8-16-1927 (Box 8)
  - Clarence Gardener to Major Putnam., 8-19-1927 (Box 8)
  - A. Henry Reinhardt to Mr. Putnam., 8-25-1927 (Box 8)
  - William Howard Taft to Major Putnam., 8-26-1927 (Box 8)
  - Foster to Major Putnam., 8-29-1927 (Box 9)
  - Elihu Root to Major Putnam., 9-2-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Sir Gregory Foster., 9-8-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Read Printing Company., 9-9-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to R. R. Bowker., 9-22-1927 (Box 9)
  - Arthur Keith to Major Putnam., 9-13-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Herbert S. Houston., 9-14-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Lord Loch., 9-15-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Sir Gregory Foster., 9-15-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Editor of the Sunday Feature of the New York World., 9-20-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Henry Goddard Leach., 9-21-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Frederick Law Olmsted, Jr., 9-21-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to John Daniels., 9-21-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam Otto Kahn., 9-26-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Logan Hay., 9-26-1927 (Box 9)
  - John Daniels to Major Putnam., 9-26-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to William H. Baldwin., 9-26-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Hon. James M. Beck., 9-27-1927 (Box 9)
  - From Putnam to John Daniels., 9-27-1927 (Box 9)
  - From H. G. Leach to Major Putnam., 9-27-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Otto H. Kahn., 9-29-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to H. C. Leach., 9-29-1927 (Box 9)
  - Clarence Gardner to Mr. Putnam., 10-14-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Professor Henry Robinson Shipman., 10-4-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Lawrence F. Abbott., 10-4-1927 (Box 9)
  - Halford L. Hoskins to Major Putnam., 10-10-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Doctor Butler., 10-10-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Prof. Halford L. Hoskins., 10-12-1927 (Box 9)
  - M. M. Murphy to Putnam., 10-13-1927 (Box 9)
  - A. W. Page's secretary to Mr. Putnam., 10-13-1927 (Box 9)
  - Paul Crane to Mr. Putnam., 10-13-1927 (Box 9)
  - John Jay Chapman to Mr. Putnam., 10-14-1927 (Box 9)
  - William Higgins to Putnam., 10-17-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Daniels., 10-18-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to John Henry Hammond., 10-20-1927 (Box 9)
  - Everett Case to Mr. Putnam., 10-20-1927 (Box 9)
  - Anna Bowman Dodd to Major Putnam., 10-25-1927 (Box 9)
  - R. E. Byrd to Major Putnam., 10-26-1927 (Box 9)
  - Elihu Root to Major., 10-28-1927 (Box 9)
  - R. E. Byrd to Major., 10-29-1927 (Box 9)
  - William Beebe to Major Putnam., 10-31-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Professor Samuel R. Bemis., 10-31-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Joe L. Clark., 10-31-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Thomas A. Edison., 10-31-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to A. B. Fitkin., 10-31-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to G. H. Jennings., 10-31-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Samuel K. Jacobs., 10-31-1927 (Box 9)
  - C. S. Stilwell to Mr. Putnam., 10-31-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Charles M. Schwab., 10-31-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Hon. John W. Davis., 11-3-1927 (Box 9)
  - Robert L. Pierrepont to Mr. Putnam., 11-3-1927 (Box 9)
  - Buckmaster to Mr. Putnam., 11-4-1927 (Box 9)
  - R. S. Brewster to Major Putnam., 11-7-1927 (Box 9)
  - F. Schuyler Matthews to Major Putnam., 11-8-1927 (Box 9)
  - Edmund Gosse to Mr. Putnam., 11-30-1927 (Box 9)
  - Walter J. Salmon to Mr. Putnam., 11-15-1927 (Box 9)
  - J. A. Keyes to Mr. Putnam., 11-19-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Mr. Tisdale., 11-22-1927 (Box 9)
  - S. M. Ward to Mr. Putnam., 11-22-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to James N. Gemble., 11-29-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Sir Gregory Foster., 12-2-1927 (Box 9)
  - Frances M. Gibbon to Major Putnam., 12-7-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Mrs. Harold I. Pratt., 12-7-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to J. N. Jarvie., 12-7-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to T. A. Havemeyer., 12-7-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Harvey S. Firestone., 12-7-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to William A. Delano., 12-7-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Mrs. W. Bayard Cutting., 12-7-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Charles A. Stone., 12-7-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Orla B. Taylor., 12-8-1927 (Box 9)
  - Francis H. Bergen to Major Putnam., 12-13-1927 (Box 9)
  - William R. Sthaler to Putnam., 12-13-1927 (Box 9)
  - Orla B. Taylor to Major., 12-15-1927 (Box 9)
  - Gregory Foster to Major Putnam., 12-17-1927 (Box 9)
  - John McBatee Bowman to Mr. Putnam., 12-20-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Otto E. Kahn., 12-22-1927 (Box 9)
  - Otto E. Kahn to Major Putnam., 12-24-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Sir Frederick Macmillian., 12-29-1927 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Guy Parsloe., 12-29-1927 (Box 9)
  - Frederick Macmillian to Putnam., 1-8-1928 (Box 9)
  - Sarah M. Bonham to Putnam., 1-11-1928 (Box 9)
  - Eugene Bagges to Major Putnam., 1-21-1928 (Box 9)
  - A. Maude Royden to Mrs. Putnam., 1-24-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Perry Belmont., 1-23-1928 (Box 9)
  - Mary B. Messer to Major Putnam., 2-2-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Hon. John W. Davis., 2-6-1928 (Box 9)
  - Secretary to Mr. Hayden to Mr. Putnam., 2-6-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Dr. Henry Seidel Canby., 2-9-1928 (Box 7)
  - Putnam to John Markle., 2-10-1928 (Box 7)
  - E. M. Schwarzl to Mr. Putnam., 2-10-1928 (Box 7)
  - A. Reikman to Putnam., 2-11-1928 (Box 7)
  - Marel I. Cadman to Major Putnam., 2-11-1928 (Box 7)
  - Irving S. Adler to Mr. Putnam., 2-11-1928 (Box 7)
  - E. Berwind to Mr. Putnam., 2-11-1928 (Box 7)
  - S. Stanwood Menken to Major Putnam., 2-11-1928 (Box 7)
  - Cassa Gilbert to Major Putnam., 2-11-1928 (Box 7)
  - Harry Emerson Fosdick to Mr. Putnam., 2-14-1928 (Box 7)
  - James Aphyer to Mr. Putnam., 2-14-1928 (Box 7)
  - Goodwin to Putnam., 2-15-1928 (Box 7)
  - H. Ruff to Putnam., 2-15-1928 (Box 7)
  - Thomas W. Lemont's secretary to Putnam., 2-15-1928 (Box 7)
  - George Wharton Pepper to Mr. Putnam., 2-15-1928 (Box 7)
  - Herbert Fairfield Osborn to Putnam., 2-16-1928 (Box 7)
  - E. C. Stuckless to Putnam., 2-17-1928 (Box 7)
  - Harry Harkness Flagler to Major Putnam., 2-17-1928 (Box 7)
  - Beatrice Farrand to Mr. Putnam., 2-17-1928 (Box 7)
  - Irving B. Richman to Major Putnam., 2-18-1928 (Box 7)
  - Putnam to Harry Harkness Flagler., 2-20-1928 (Box 7)
  - Putnam to Henry Fairfield Osborn., 2-21-1928 (Box 7)
  - A. B. Farquhar Co. Ltd. to Mr. Putnam., 2-22-1928 (Box 7)
  - Williams to Mr. Putnam., 2-23-1928 (Box 7)
  - Williams to Mr. Putnam., 2-23-1928 (Box 7)
  - J. A. Johnston to Putnam., 2-23-1928 (Box 7)
  - P.S. du Pont. to Mr. Putnam., 2-24-1928 (Box 7)
  - A. M. Roydon to Mrs. Putnam., 2-24-1928 (Box 7)
  - A. W. Neall to Mr. Putnam., 2-24-1928 (Box 7)
  - J. A. Keyes to Mr. Putnam., 2-25-1928 (Box 7)
  - Gifford Pinchot to Mr. Putnam., 2-27-1928 (Box 9)
  - Mrs. E. H. Harriman's secretary to Mr. Putnam., 2-28-1928 (Box 9)
  - Dunsany to Major Putnam., 2-29-1928 (Box 9)
  - Gregory Foster to Major Putnam., 3-1-1928 (Box 9)
  - James B. Colgate to Putnam., 3-2-1928 (Box 9)
  - Jennings to Mr. Putnam., 3-2-1928 (Box 9)
  - Robert Seager to Putnam., 3-5-1928 (Box 9)
  - Beatrace H. Borden to Mr. Putnam., 3-5-1928 (Box 9)
  - Simon Guggenhiem's secretary to Mr. Putnam., 3-9-1928 (Box 9)
  - Robert L. Gerry to Mr. Putnam., 3-12-1928 (Box 9)
  - John H. Finley to Mr. Putnam. "Avatar of the Century Club.", 3-15-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to David Kinley., 3-16-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to John McF. Howie., 3-16-1928 (Box 9)
  - John McFarlane Howie to Major., 3-17-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to the Editor of The Times., 3-17-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Lord Loch., 3-19-1928 (Box 9)
  - David Kinley to Major Putnam., 3-19-1928 (Box 9)
  - Sophie C. Hadide to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 3-21-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Albert St. Peter., 3-23-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Gen. R. I. Bullard., 3-27-1928 (Box 9)
  - Albert St. Peter to Major Putnam., 3-30-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Albert St. Peter., 3-31-1928 (Box 9)
  - Artemas Ward, Jr. to Putnam., 4-4-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Hon. A. H. Vestal., 4-5-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Vestal (copy)., 4-5-1928 (Box 9)
  - H. R. Waddell to Putnam., 4-24-1928 (Box 9)
  - Frederick Macmillan to Putnam., 4-28-1928 (Box 9)
  - Lord Loch to Major Putnam., 4-26-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to The Hon. Charles F. Schwab., 5-2-1928 (Box 9)
  - Frank C. Ayres, the Business Historical Society, to Putnam., 5-7-1928 (Box 9)
  - Frances M. Gibbon to Major Putnam., 5-15-1928 (Box 9)
  - Charnwood to Major Putnam., 5-18-1928 (Box 9)
  - S. G. Patterson to Dr. Putnam., 6-1-1928 (Box 9)
  - C. A. Brooke-Cunningham to Major Putnam., 6-8-1928 (Box 9)
  - Frederick Macmillan to Putnam., 6-11-1928 (Box 9)
  - Katherine Kirchner to Putnam., 6-18-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Henry Robinson Shipman., 6-19-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Charles F. Brush., 6-22-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Alfred Cowles., 6-22-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Kenyon Y. Painter., 6-22-1928 (Box 9)
  - C. W. Quinn to Mr. Putnam., 6-22-1928 (Box 9)
  - William T. Manning to Major Putnam., 6-22-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Mrs. Aten, Brooks-Bright Foundation, 6-25-1928 (Box 9)
  - John Henry Hammond to Major Putnam., 6-25-1928 (Box 9)
  - Harry Harknass Flagler to Major Putnam., 6-25-1928 (Box 9)
  - George A. Plimpton to Mr. Putnam., 6-25-1928 (Box 9)
  - J. W. Hileman to Major Putnam., 6-25-1928 (Box 9)
  - Logan Hay to Major Putnam., 6-26-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Otto H. Kahn., 6-26-1928 (Box 9)
  - John F. O'Keefe to Putnam., 6-27-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Hon. Andrew W. Mellon., 6-29-1928 (Box 9)
  - Cara L. Broughton to Major Putnam., 7-5-1928 (Box 9)
  - J. Frederick Talcott to Major., 7-9-1928 (Box 9)
  - Donald M. Brodie to Mr. Putnam., 7-11-1928 (Box 9)
  - Ross Howell for Charles H. Swift to Mr. Putnam., 7-12-1928 (Box 9)
  - James S. Lang to Putnam., 7-12-1928 (Box 9)
  - R. Sheriff to Major Putnam., 7-13-1928 (Box 9)
  - D. Auller to Major Putnam., 7-14-1928 (Box 9)
  - From John F. Forest., 7-19-1928 (Box 9)
  - H. G. Leach to Major Putnam., 7-19-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to John D. Rockefeller., 7-19-1928 (Box 9)
  - Alice Greenough Townsend to Mr. Putnam., 7-20-1928 (Box 9)
  - Frederick Strauss to Otto Kahn., 7-25-1928 (Box 9)
  - Samuel Mather to Mr. Putnam., 7-23-1928 (Box 9)
  - Melina Wilson to Putnam., 7-23-1928 (Box 9)
  - Otto Kahn to Major Putnam., 7-27-1928 (Box 9)
  - Secretary to Gerard B. Lambert to Putnam., 7-27-1928 (Box 9)
  - Elizabeth Goldsmith to Major Putnam., 7-31-1928 (Box 9)
  - Frederick A. Jullian to Putnam., 8-3-1928 (Box 9)
  - Louise Hyde for Mrs. Henry James to Major Putnam., 8-5-1928 (Box 9)
  - R. W. Leonard to Major., 8-6-1928 (Box 9)
  - W. F. Sinclair to Putnam., 8-6-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to F. Kingsbury Curtis., 8-8-1928 (Box 9)
  - Irenee du Pont to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 8-30-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Otto H. Kahn., 8-31-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Hon. James M. Beck., 9-10-1928 (Box 9)
  - N. R. Cole to Major Putnam., 9-10-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Florence Brooks-Aten., 9-10-1928 (Box 9)
  - William H. Baldwing to Barbara S. Quin., 9-12-1928 (Box 9)
  - Anna Bowman Dodd to Major Putnam., 9-17-1928 (Box 9)
  - Otto H. Kahn to Major Putnam., 9-18-1928 (Box 9)
  - Bertha B. Sturgis to Mr. MarGillivray., 9-23-1928 (Box 9)
  - W. O. Hefferman to Putnam., 9-26-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Henry H. MacCracken., 9-28-1928 (Box 9)
  - Ernest Benn to Major Putnam., 9-28-1928 (Box 9)
  - Thomas B. Appleget to Mr. Putnam., 10-1-1928 (Box 9)
  - From Dunsany., 10-3-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to William H. Baldwin., 10-4-1928 (Box 9)
  - Wilhjalmer Stefansson to Major Putnam., 10-4-1928 (Box 9)
  - Jack Crawford to Major Putnam., 10-8-1928 (Box 9)
  - W. H. Baldwin to Major Putnam., 10-9-1928 (Box 9)
  - W. H. Woodin to Mr. Putnam., 10-11-1928 (Box 9)
  - C. Reinold Noyes to Mr. Putnam., 10-12-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Lady Astor., 10-13-1928 (Box 9)
  - Robert Wilberforce to Major Putnam., 10-13-1928 (Box 9)
  - Walter S. Gifford to Mr. Putnam., 10-18-1928 (Box 9)
  - O. B. Maddox to Putnam., 10-20-1928 (Box 9)
  - Jane Farrell to Putnam., 10-23-1928 (Box 9)
  - C. E. Mitchell to Mr. Putnam., 10-26-1928 (Box 9)
  - Harold M. Swift., 11-1-1928 (Box 9)
  - A. H. Harris to Major Putnam., 11-1-1928 (Box 9)
  - Earl D. Babet to Mr. Putnam., 11-2-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Whitney Warren., 11-3-1928 (Box 9)
  - John M. Willys to Mr. Putnam., 11-5-1928 (Box 9)
  - Johnston de Forest to Mr. Putnam., 11-5-1928 (Box 9)
  - Charles E. Bodaux to Putnam., 11-5-1928 (Box 9)
  - John McEntee Bowman to Mr. Putnam., 11-7-1928 (Box 9)
  - A. A. _ for P. A. Rockefeller to Putnam., 11-10-1928 (Box 9)
  - From Harold H. Swift., 11-12-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Nicholas Murray Butler., 11-14-1928 (Box 9)
  - Julian Hawthorne to Putnam., 11-16-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Editor of "The Public Ledger.", 11-17-1928 (Box 9)
  - Secretary to Mr. Salvage to Putnam., 11-20-1928 (Box 9)
  - George D. Pratt to Putnam., 11-21-1928 (Box 9)
  - R. Barkan to Putnam., 11-21-1928 (Box 9)
  - James Phillips to Mr. Putnam., 11-23-1928 (Box 9)
  - F. A. Wood to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 11-24-1928 (Box 9)
  - Otto H. Kahn to Major Putnam., 11-28-1928 (Box 9)
  - R. K. Wood to Mr. Putnam., 11-30-1928 (Box 9)
  - Major Putnam to Francee M. Gibbon, 12-30-1928 (Box 9)
  - Ernest Ludwig to Major Putnam., 12-1-1928 (Box 9)
  - Albert S. Scott to Mr. Putnam., 12-3-1928 (Box 9)
  - Roy Chapman Andrews to Dr. Putnam., 12-5-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Prof. James T. Shatwell., 12-20-1928 (Box 9)
  - John W. Davis to Major., 12-20-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Frederick R. Codert., 12-26-1928 (Box 9)
  - C. E. Denney to Putnam., 12-26-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Paul Gravath., 12-27-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to George Eastman., 12-28-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Lincoln Cromwell., 12-28-1928 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Howard S. Cans., 12-28-1928 (Box 9)
  - Askworth to Putnam., 1-8-1929 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Paul Cravath., 1-11-1929 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Otto Kahn., 1-11-1929 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Otto Kahn., 1-11-1929 (Box 9)
  - C. A. Bliss to Mr. Putnam., 1-3-1929 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to F. R. Coudert., 1-11-1929 (Box 9)
  - W. H. Baldwin to Major Putnam., 1-15-1929 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to William H. Baldwin., 1-16-1929 (Box 9)
  - John W. Davis to Major., 1-16-1929 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to John E. J. Fanshawe., 1-17-1929 (Box 9)
  - W. T. Sinclair to Putnam., 1-18-1929 (Box 9)
  - S. A. Salvage to Major Putnam., 1-21-1929 (Box 9)
  - James F. Harris to Putnam., 1-21-1929 (Box 9)
  - Gertrude Moore to Mr. Putnam., 1-21-1929 (Box 9)
  - Nicholas Murray Butler to Major Putnam., 1-23-1929 (Box 9)
  - R. Lambert to Major., 2-4-1929 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Barron G. Collier., 2-8-1929 (Box 9)
  - John Daniels to Major Putnam., 2-11-1929 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Mrs. Margaret P. Morey., 2-14-1929 (Box 9)
  - John B. Barnham to Mr. MacGillivary., 2-14-1929 (Box 9)
  - Dwight _an to Mr. Putnam., 2-25-1929 (Box 9)
  - John B. Burnham to Mr. MacGillivary., 2-27-1929 (Box 9)
  - Unknown., 2-1929 (Box 9)
  - Howard S. Gans to Major Putnam., 2-28-1929 (Box 9)
  - Mrs. Beebe to Major Putnam., 3-2-1929 (Box 9)
  - John G. Winant's secretary to Putnam., 3-4-1929 (Box 9)
  - Dunsany to Major Putnam., 3-9-1929 (Box 9)
  - S. F. Orza to Major Putnam., 3-13-1929 (Box 9)
  - Margaret Eyre Rothwell to Major Putnam., 3-24-1929 (Box 9)
  - Samuel E. Fisher to Mr. Putnam., 4-6-1929 (Box 9)
  - Caroline A. Flexner to Mr. Putnam, 4-6-1929 (Box 9)
  - Unknown to Major Putnam., 4-9-1929 (Box 9)
  - Albert Perry Brigham to Major Putnam., 4-13-1929 (Box 9)
  - Clarence W. Bowen to Major Putnam., 4-13-1929 (Box 9)
  - Herbert H. Lehman to Major Putnam., 4-22-1929 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Rev. Samuel Parkes Cadman., 5-8-1929 (Box 9)
  - Robert J. Gladwell to Major Putnam., 5-22-1929 (Box 9)
  - Samuel (?) Parrish to Major Putnam., 6-7-1929 (Box 9)
  - Lord Enworth (?) to Mr. Putnam., 6-11-1929 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to Allen Forbes., 7-19-1929 (Box 9)
  - Eloise D. Pepper to Mr. Putnam., 7-24-1929 (Box 9)
  - George W. Coor to Mr. Putnam., 7-26-1929 (Box 9)
  - E. Kent Hubbard to Mr. Putnam., 7-26-1929 (Box 9)
  - F. E. Conrad to Mr. Putnam., 7-29-1929 (Box 9)
  - H. W. de Forest to Mr. Putnam., 7-31-1929 (Box 9)
  - H. W. de Forest to Mr. Putnam., 7-31-1929 (Box 9)
  - Ollie Chastervort to Putnam., 7-31-1929 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to H. W. de Forest., 8-5-1929 (Box 9)
  - Putnam to M. F. McClelland., 8-5-1929 (Box 9)
  - Elihu Root to Major., 12-9-1929 (Box 9)
  - James T. Shotwell to Mr. Putnam., 12-29-1929 (Box 9)
  - C. M. B. Quennel to Major Putnam., 1-23-1930 (Box 9)
  - Oscor Newfang to Major Putnam., 1-31-1930 (Box 9)
  - John Collier to Dr. Emerson., 3-10-1931 (Box 9)
  - Francis C. Wilson to Percy Jackson., 5-20-1931 (Box 9)
  - Oliver La Farge to Mrs. Smith., 6-22-1931 (Box 9)
  - R. J. Hagerman to Meredith Hare., 4-27-1931 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, 194 pieces., undated (Box 9)
- PUBLISHED MATERIAL:
  - Pamphlets:
    - American Indian Life. Bulletin No. 18. San Francisco and Washington., 7-1931 (Box 10)
    - The Book Buyer's Manual: a Catalogue of Foreign and American Books in Every Department of Literature. New York, George P. Putnam and Co., 1853 (Box 10)
    - Clearance and Remainder Sale of Books and Electrotype Plates to be sold at auction without reserve by Bangs and Co. New York., 2-11-1895 (Box 10)
    - A Declaration of Interdependence: Commemoration in London of the 4th of July, 1776. The Library of War Literature, New York. 21 copies., 1918 (Box 10)
    - Ethical Addresses. Memorial Exercises in Honor of the late Octavius Brooks Rrothingham., 12-1895 (Box 10)
    - The Growth of the Censorship Idea. By George Haven Putnam, president, the American Rights League. The Independent., 1923 (Box 10)
    - Independence Day in London. Hodder and Stoughton, London, Toronto, New York., 1918 (Box 10)
    - International Copyright, Considered in Some of its Relations to Ethics and Political Economy. By George Haven Putnam. G. P. Putnam's Sons, New York., 1879 (Box 10)
    - Literary Property. By George Haven Putnam. A. H. Andrews and Co., Chicago, 1884. 2 copies. (Box 10)
    - Lucian the Sophist. By Emily James Putnam. Reprinted from "Classical Philology," Vol. IV. No. 12., 4-1909 (Box 10)
    - Messenger. Vol. VI, No. 4., 4-1929 (Box 10)
    - The Prophylaxis of Insanity. By Mary Putnam Jacobi. Reprinted from the "Archives of Medicine." New York, G. P. Putnam's Sons., 10-1881 (Box 10)
    - Putnam's Magazine of Literature, Science, Art and National Interests. Vol. IV, No. IX., 8-1869 (Box 10)
    - G. P. Putnam's New Publications., 3-1849 (Box 10)
    - The Quick in the "Dead." by Herbert Putnam. Reprinted from "University of California Chronicle," Vol. XIV, No. 2. (Box 10)
    - Robert Fruin, 1823-1899, a Memorial Sketch. By Ruth Putnam. Reprinted from "Annual Report of the American Historical Association for 1899," Vol. I. Washington GPO., 1900 (Box 10)
    - The Roman Index and its Latent Historian. By Joseph Hilgers. Reprinted from "Catholic Fortnightly Review.", 1908 (Box 10)
    - Specialism in Medicine. By Mary Putnam Jacobi, M. D. Reprinted from "Archives of Medicine." New York, G. P. Putnam's Sons., 2-1882 (Box 10)
  - Periodicals:
    - Alma Mater. Partial copy. Article by George Haven Putnam. (Box 11)
    - The American Review of Reviews. Article by George Haven Putnam. "Franklin Delano Roosevelt. Democratic Candidate for the Vice-Presidency.", 9-1920 (Box 11)
    - The American Review of Reviews. Article by George Haven Putnam. "The Civil War Fifty Years After." (Box 11)
    - The American Review of Reviews. Article by George Haven Putnam. "The Prince of Wales Visits American." (Box 11)
    - The American Stationer. Article by George Haven Putnam, "The Publisher.", 4-23-1896 (Box 11)
    - The Annals of the American Academy. Article by George Haven Putnam, "Politics as a Barrier to an Adequate and Efficient System of National Defence." (Box 11)
    - The Book Monthly. Partial copy, article reviewing George Haven Putnam's book, "Sword and Pen." (Box 11)
    - The Bookman. Partial copy, including "Cencorship," by George Haven Putnam. 2 copies. (Box 11)
    - The Bookman. Partial copy, with "Eight Books of the Month," reviewed by George Haven Putnam. (Box 11)
    - Books of the Day. Review. "An Erring Woman's Love, by Ella Wheeler Wilcox." (Box 11)
    - The Bookseller. "Trade and Literary Gossip," with a review of his book, "A Prisoner of War in Virginia in 1864-5.", 8-6-1915 (Box 11)
    - The Bookseller. "Mr. George Haven Putnam on Fifty Years of American Publishing.", 6-14-1906 (Box 11)
    - Boston Medical and Surgical Journal. "Obituary - Mary Putnam Jacobi, M.D.", 10-27-1909 (Box 11)
    - The Catalogue. "The Evolution of the Copyright Law," by George Haven Putnam., 10-27-1909 (Box 11)
    - Chicago Inter Ocean. Clip of review of George Haven Putnam's book., 8-17-1912 (Box 11)
    - The Christian Union. Vol. XII, No. 24. "Mr. Pennyman." by George Haven Putnam., 8-17-1912 (Box 11)
    - The Critic. With "The Copyright Law of the United States and the Authors of the Continent," by George Haven Putnam., 4-9-1912 (Box 11)
    - Daily Chronicle. Clip of review of George Haven Putnam's book., 2-1-1919. (Box 11)
    - English Speaking World. "The Duty of the English Speaking Peoples in the U. S. How the English Speaking Union Can Promote the Great Joint Interests of All Nations," by George Haven Putnam., 2-1-1919 (Box 11)
    - The Evening Post: New York. Saturday. "Knuckerbocker Centenary," by George Haven Putnam., 10-16-1909 (Box 11)
    - The Evening Post: New York. Two Clips, "Putnam Predicts Rise in the Price of Books," and Charles Collins," both by George Haven Putnam. (Box 11)
    - The Evening Sun. Clipping., 2-20-1917 (Box 11)
    - The Forum. "Washington Irving," by George Haven Putnam. (Box 11)
    - Free Press. Clipping of review of George Haven Putnam's book., 10-5-1912 (Box 11)
    - The Graphic. "The Leaves of Yesterday, a Book Page for Tomorrow," an article about George Haven Putnam, by James Milne. 2 copies., 7-5-1919 (Box 11)
    - The Independent. "The Book Trust and the Copyright Bill - A Publisher's Defense," by George Haven Putnam. (Box 11)
    - The Independent. "Jefferson Davis and the Fight for the Republic," by George Haven Putnam. Vol. 110. No. 3836. 3 copies, partial. (Box 11)
    - Journal of the National Institute of Social Sciences. Reprint, New York. "The Free Traders of America, Their Ideals, Their Policy and Their Immediate Aims," by George Haven Putnam., 4-1918 (Box 11)
    - The Kansas City Star Magazine. Vol. 1, No. 33. "My Memories of Washington Irving," by George Haven Putnam., 3-8-1925 (Box 11)
    - The Kansas City Star Magazine. "Literary Relations of England and America," by George Haven Putnam., 10-11-1925 (Box 11)
    - The Landmark. "Literature and International Relations," by George Haven Putnam. (Box 11)
    - Law and Labor. "The British General Strike and the Coal Dispute," by George Haven Putnam., 7-1926. (Box 11)
    - The Library Journal. "Copyright in its Relations to Libraries," a summary of remarks by George Haven Putnam., 2-1909 (Box 11)
    - The Literary Digest. "Reviews of New Books - General Wilson's Recollections of the Civil War," by George Haven Putnam., 3-1-1913 (Box 11)
    - Liverpool Echo. Clip, review of George Haven Putnam's book., 11-30-1912 (Box 11)